onlinemictest.com 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy | OnlineMicTest

### Advertising Privacy Statement

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site. AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: https://adssettings.google.com. You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: http://optout.networkadvertising.org. However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

### For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing. If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at **ilanflint@gmail.com** and contact AdThrive at **info@adthrive.com**. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

## General Privacy Policy:

Online Mic Test (“ **Online Mic Test** “) operates onlinemictest.com and may operate other websites. It is Online Mic Test’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Online Mic Test collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Online Mic Test’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Online Mic Test’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Online Mic Test may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Online Mic Test also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on onlinemictest.com blogs/sites. Online Mic Test only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Online Mic Test’s websites choose to interact with Online Mic Test in ways that require Online Mic Test to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Online Mic Test gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at onlinemictest.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Online Mic Test are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Online Mic Test collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Online Mic Test. Online Mic Test does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Online Mic Test may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Online Mic Test may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Online Mic Test does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Online Mic Test discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Online Mic Test’s behalf or to provide services available at Online Mic Test’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Online Mic Test’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Online Mic Test will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Online Mic Test discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Online Mic Test believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Online Mic Test, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Online Mic Test website and have supplied your email address, Online Mic Test may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Online Mic Test and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Online Mic Test takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Online Mic Test uses cookies to help Online Mic Test identify and track visitors, their usage of Online Mic Test website, and their website access preferences. Online Mic Test visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Online Mic Test’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Online Mic Test’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Online Mic Test, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Online Mic Test goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Online Mic Test may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Online Mic Test and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Online Mic Test may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Online Mic Test’s sole discretion. Online Mic Test encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a onlinemictest.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
